<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Yep. this is my &#39;Other blog&#39;</title>
    <link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Yep. this is my &#39;Other blog&#39;</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Men Are From Mars</title>
      <link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/blog/men-are-from-mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/blog/men-are-from-mars/</guid>
      <description>Men Are From Mars, Women are from Venus - John Gray the two biggest mistakes we make in relating to the opposite sex: men mistakenly offer solutions and invalidate feelings while women offer unsolicited advice and direction.
Men are motivated when they feel needed while women are motivated when they feel cherished.
Men primarily need a kind of love that is trusting, accepting, and appreciative. Women primarily need a kind of love that is caring, understanding, and respectful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lovelanguages</title>
      <link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/blog/lovelanguages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/blog/lovelanguages/</guid>
      <description>The 5 Love Language - Gary Chapman People speak different love languages.
We must be willing to learn our spouse’s primary love language if we are to be effective communicators of love.
Something in our nature cries out to be loved by another.
After studying scores of couples, she concluded that the average life span of a romantic obsession is two years. If it is a secretive love affair, it may last a little longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Models</title>
      <link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/blog/models/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/blog/models/</guid>
      <description>Models - Mark Manson Emerson once wrote, &amp;ldquo;What you do speaks so loudly I cannot hear what you say.&amp;rdquo;
 Your movement or lack of movement reflects and alters emotions, not the words. Words are the side-effect. Sex is the side-effect. The game is emotions, emotions through movement. If you learn anything from this book, let that be it.
As a man, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to actually be rich and famous, you just have to show a lot of potential for being rich and famous to be considered extremely attractive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TinyBeautifulThings</title>
      <link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/blog/tinybeautifulthings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/blog/tinybeautifulthings/</guid>
      <description>Tiny Beautiful Things - Cheryl Strayed Because we are all, in the private kingdom of our hearts, desperate for the company of a wise, true friend. Someone who isn’t embarrassed by our emotions, or her own, who recognizes that life is short and that all we have to offer, in the end, is love.
When I was done writing it, I understood that things happened just as they were meant to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>