<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Infj on Yep. this is my &#39;Other blog&#39;</title>
    <link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Infj on Yep. this is my &#39;Other blog&#39;</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2017 Alamgir Qazi</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>tipsforINFJ2</title>
      <link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/tipsforinfj2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/tipsforinfj2/</guid>
      <description>Tips for INFJ (2)  It’s okay to love yourself as much as you love everyone else. Have self-respect. Don’t feel like you’re inconveniencing people when you ask for help. It’s the right thing to do and they will understand. It’s okay to say no. Don’t waste your life worrying about the world’s problems. They’re not your fault and you can’t solve them yourself anyway. You are a sensitive one, and it is best to keep yourself out of situations or relationships where you will be overwhelmed or have your heart broken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tipsforINFJ3</title>
      <link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/tipsforinfj3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/tipsforinfj3/</guid>
      <description>Tips for INFJ (3)  Stay strong. Being an INFJ can be very difficult and stressful at times. There will be parts of your life where you feel extremely lonely or you think about all the regrets you have in life. These negative thoughts can hinder you and even pull you down a deep hole. You’ll have to remind yourself that you need to be strong not only for your friends and family but for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tipsforINFJ4</title>
      <link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/tipsforinfj4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/tipsforinfj4/</guid>
      <description>Tips for INFJ (4)  If you are an INFJ, I’d like to congratulate you first of all, for falling into the category of the rarest of all types (&amp;lt;2%). Secondly, be prepared to read what I’m going to tell you-
LIFE IS HARDEST FOR INFJs.
Yes!
Why?
Let me frame an example.
Do you see those long faced street vendors nobody buys anything from?
Those senile men and women wistfully living lives, having been kicked out of their own homes by their own off springs?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tipsforINFJ5</title>
      <link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/tipsforinfj5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/tipsforinfj5/</guid>
      <description>Tips for INFJ (5)  When I think of some life tips for myself and those like me , I would think:
Stop worrying. I’m always worrying about something. God damn it, there are so many things to worry about in life. Especially when you&amp;rsquo;re an INFJ who tends to take on the problems of others, but don’t. The more you worry, the less you enjoy life, and the less you can work on the things that worry you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tipsforINFJ1</title>
      <link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/tipsforinfj1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/otherblog/infj/tipsforinfj1/</guid>
      <description>Tips for INFJ (1)  Dear INFJ,
I know it&amp;rsquo;s difficult. Being in the world is very difficult. Existing is very difficult. I know you always look forward to running away from everything, from everyone, maybe from yourself. I know you are looking for something bigger, something beyond all what you know or everyone know. I know nothing will satisfy you in the dust and ashes of this world. So, dear, look for it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>